So, Dillon, there's something
I've been wondering.
Who do you like best?
Zeki Muren?
Ajda Pekkan?
Or maybe you're more
of a Baris Manco guy?
Hmm?
I thought you wanted
to start a Turkish-focused
music streaming business?
I did. I do.
And you needed
Demir's musical expertise,
as well as his funding,
business infrastructure.
But, no.
You provided good looks and charm.
Oh, I don't know about that one.
I mean, Demir was a pretty
good-looking guy.
And you don't seem too charming.
Is that why Demir pulled out?
You went ahead anyway,
didn't you, Dillon?
Raising money using his brand
and family name.
But then Demir found out.
It was a misunderstanding.
It looks more like fraud, Dillon,
which I believe you have
a lot of experience with. Right?
It says here Dillon Irving
is wanted on charges
of larceny by embezzlement
and identity fraud.
Wanted by the United States
government.
Dillon, that doesn't sound good. OK.
This is all true,
but I didn't kill Demir.
I liked Demir. Why would I do that?
The inheritance.
You know, when Erol dies,
your sister gets everything
and you can continue
leeching off her
like you have done your entire life.
The Karagul family has a leech
for sure, but it's not me.
Cem.
Cem's got a side hustle
lifting stuff
from the house and auctioning
it off.
But then Demir caught him
and he took it to Erol, but...
..the old man refused to believe
Cem will betray him.
Dillon's a conman.
He's playing us to frame Cem.
He may well be a grifter, but does
he seem like a murderer to you?
He looked terrified to me.
Anyway, no-one knows
about Muzo's auction house cash.
Dillon couldn't have known it would
implicate Cem so strongly. Yep.
There is a long property
trail in Cem Kartal's name.
So maybe Dillon's right
about Cem's side hustle,
which would make him a regular
at the auction house.
What I'm certain of is,
whoever is behind all this
is resourceful,
manipulative, tenacious
and still extremely dangerous.
# Bir seyler var, bir seyler var
# Bir seyler var, anlatmadigin
# Bir seyler var, konusmadigin
# Yasakladigin ve sakladigin
# Bir seyler var, bir seyler yok
# Bir seyler az, bir seyler cok
# Bunu zavalli beynine sok
# Bir seyler sensiz devam ediyor. #
Good morning, everyone.
Chief Inspector Buchar
has given us 48 hours
to decide if it's Cem or Dillon.
Suleyman, expand your
background check
on all the members
of the Karagul staff.
Tarik, get into
the auction house CCTV,
see if the Muzo cash trail
leads anywhere,
even if it's back to Dillon.
So are you bringing Cem in?
We need answers fast.
Ayse, you're with me.
Oh.
Erol is asleep.
Maybe we could talk.
He's been deteriorating
since Demir's death.
I'd hoped it was just grief,
but his strength
and his lucidity is just...
He's in the final phase.
I'm sorry.
I guess there are certain things
that are beyond our control.
Indeed.
Can you tell me a little about how
you actually became Erol's nurse?
His old nurse was in
the same agency as I was,
and when she left
she recommended me.
She's a good friend.
May I?
My son.
What's his name?
Constantine.
Families like this don't like you
having independence.
They want to know that you can
fully dedicate yourself to them.
So you hid your son from Cem?
He's with my cousins
back in Tiraspol.
I send my salary back.
You won't tell them...
No.
The argument you had
the other day with Cem,
what was that about, specifically?
He's my boss.
Lina, think of Erol.
Learning what happened to Demir
might give him comfort,
even strength.
He was asking about Dillon.
He wanted me to watch him,
to talk to him.
Like a spy.
And I said I didn't want to.
I didn't want to get involved.
I just wanted to do my job and...
He wasn't happy. Why spy on Dillon?
Honestly?
Yes, please.
Because Cem doesn't like Dillon.
And after Demir's death...
..he's just looking
for someone to blame.
Catch!
MOBILE PHONE RINGS
Cetin Ikmen.
Nobody's shown up.
I was here earlier.
Nothing.
We've been conned, man.
Emir doesn't know Kayra Khan.
Just fancied an easy payday.
Let's get your money back at least.
He'll tell Ikmen.
MESSAGE ALERT
Well, that's good at least.
The keys are ready
for Leyla's old apartment.
This was your apartment
after you left London.
Your dad owns it.
I thought maybe
we could spark something.
A memory about what you
were working on before.
Maybe there's something here.
Something only you can find.
I'll give it a try.
How long did I live here?
About a year.
Hmm.
Nice.
Oh, God.
I look like crap.
No. You don't.
Still not sleeping?
Same nightmare every night.
What?!
Well, who knew it would take
a massive head injury
for me to realise that leopard-print
is just not my thing?!
You know, you wore that
the last night we went to Fabric.
Did I? Yeah, you looked cool.
OK.
I guess I'll have to take
your word for it.
MOBILE PHONE RINGS
I love him. He is my baby brother.
And, yes, he can be
a lying piece of crap
that would cheat you out of your
savings, but he's not a killer.
Well, we don't know how desperate he
was. How deep into scamming Demir.
No.
Why did you want to talk to him?
I need to tell him that this is it.
And of course we'll help him,
you know, with the finances
and legal fees,
but I have to look after
my baby now.
I'm wondering about money.
What?
As in who controls it? Mm-hm.
Well, Erol. Only Erol?
Yes. I mean, I buy something
on Amazon and he knows about it.
What has this got to do with Dillon?
Please just answer the question.
I did answer the question.
Erol controls everything.
I mean, he...
He did make Demir signatory,
joint oversight of the business
accounts maybe three months ago.
With Erol's illness,
it just made sense.
Erol wanted Demir to be ready.
What did Cem Kartal make of that?
Cem? Mm.
Why are you asking about him?
Well, Cem is very close to Erol.
Absolutely nothing happens
in that house
without Erol
running it past Cem first.
What was Demir Karagul's
perspective...
..on Cem's level of influence?
He was used to it, I guess.
And how did Cem feel about Demir
suddenly having oversight
of the finances?
I guess you'll have to ask him that.
Can I see my brother now, please?
Mm-hm. Sure.
Officer.
He'll take you to Dillon.
Thank you.
Disgusting.
Beer?
Sure. Mehmet?
No, thank you. They're going to be
wondering where I am.
There must be some glasses
around here somewhere.
What?
These photos in London,
I look so happy.
Why did I come here?
Your career.
You were having a hard time
establishing yourself in London.
Thought Istanbul might give you
better opportunities.
What about us?
It was hard, but...
..I understood.
Look, I need to get back to work.
Right, yeah.
So what haven't we covered?
OK, so tell me again what I said?
You said you were working
on an international crime story,
reaching everywhere.
It was something dark,
and you told me to trust no-one.
Oh.
Sorry. I'm sorry I wasted your time.
Please, stop apologising.
You hate apologising. You always
called it the English disease.
Well, I was right.
It is annoying.
Shit. Wasn't there...
I was sure there was
a little table here.
It's on the other side.
Oh.
But that felt...
..right.
Unless I moved it.
Why would you do that?
Either feng shui...
..or to cover something up.
The boards are loose.
Here.
What happened to you?
I got Istanbuled.
Got my foot run over by a motorbike
and spent two hours
in emergency services
for them to tell me it's a bone
bruise and give me an ibuprofen.
Oh, sorry. Hmm.
I presume Ikmen and Ayse
have gone home?
Yeah.
You tell them I went for food?
Cool.
Well, enjoy.
Better late than never. Hey.
Look both ways before you cross.
See you in the morning.
How are we doing?
I've tried everything,
but nothing has cracked it.
Spydering doesn't work,
brute force will take forever.
I need a piece of equipment.
There is a place in Vefa
I can go and try to...
MOBILE PHONE RINGS
Sorry.
Hey. Oh, wow, you answered.
Tarik got the facial recognition
software working.
I'm sending it through now.
That's Cem.
On the 22nd of March.
The same day that matches
the serial number on Muzo's cash.
Well, we've got enough evidence,
so we're going to the Karagul
house now to bring Cem in.
You're welcome to join us.
You know, unless you're too busy
getting baklava from London again.
I've got to go.
Vefa, sounds promising.
All right.
SHE SPEAKS IN TURKISH
HE SPEAKS IN TURKISH
Detective.
We need you to come to the station.
HE SPEAKS IN TURKISH
To answer some questions
about the murder of Demir Karagul.
Fine. Lead the way, detective.
Erol Bey.
We need to talk about Demir's death.
Demir was murdered...
..because he presented
an obstacle to Erol Bey.
I think the murderer
is after your family's fortune.
And sadly, we suspected
someone close to you.
Fortune.
The fortune is rotten.
Erol Bey, are you all right?
"The sins of the father...
.."shall be visited upon the son."
I should have done more.
He's not OK, is he?
Not today.
And what about Dillon?
I mean, you just arrested Cem,
right, so...
Mrs Karagul, please.
Whatever happens
with our investigation,
your brother will be extradited
to the United States.
That is out of our hands.
Please, sit down.
Now, as you said, you have
to focus on your new family.
Do you think he'll be OK?
He's about to become a father again.
He is deteriorating so fast,
especially since his collapse.
Are you a Christian?
No.
This is your apartment.
27 Siri Street, first floor.
Your name is on the deeds,
also on number 29.
Yes, they are mine. I rent them out.
Estimated value of those
two properties is $2 million.
We've also been informed that
you paid for those apartments
by auctioning off stolen items
from the Karagul collection.
That is a scandalous lie.
But that's what Demir thought,
isn't it? You're a thief?
What with him trying to get you
sacked a week before his death?
I'm not sitting here listening
to these baseless accusations.
OK, well, how about
some evidence then?
Let's have a look at these.
See just how baseless
the accusations are then.
This is you at the Guzelbahce
auction house on the 22nd of March.
You're a regular there,
according to the auction house.
And on that same day, you sold
an item for a different reason.
You needed cash...
..to pay a boy called Muzo
to kill Demir.
No. No? No, I didn't.
This is the evidence against me?
Do you have my fingerprints
on Muzo's money?
A witness who saw me pay him?
So what if I was there
on the 22nd of March?
I'm a regular client.
Erol just gives you these items to
sell and lets you pocket the money?
I don't know, doesn't seem likely.
Do you really think Erol wouldn't
find out
if I was selling from
his collection?
How do you explain it, then?
He and I met in the army, you know.
One night, we were near the Iraqi
border and I got us lost.
I was a cocky, stupid young man.
Much like yourself.
It was dark.
Razor-sharp rocks.
I slipped and shattered
both my ankles.
But that man...
..picked me up and carried me
for miles on his back.
You are right about one thing.
There is a thief in the house.
Some antique watches
belonging to Erol's father
went missing last month.
But you need to understand, Erol
could have left me there that night.
I owe him my life.
And I'll tell you the most valuable
thing he's always allowed me.
Dignity.
Don't buy it. He stole those things.
Unfortunately,
Erol Karagul is in no state
to confirm or deny Cem's story.
Yeah, and he knows that.
Wait, wait.
OK, this is
the auction house catalogue.
Two 1920s antique watches
on sale at 3pm.
Cem was there at 10am.
No trace of him in the afternoon.
OK, so what do we do now?
Let him go. No way, no.
Without the link to Muzo's money,
we have nothing against him.
Which is why, when we release him,
you're going to follow him.
Yes?
Puzzling.
What is?
This morning,
Erol Karagul quoted the Bible.
"The sins of the father
are visited upon the son."
But I think he was trying to
tell me something. Tell you what?
But then I saw the father's portrait
and it dawned on me.
What if Erol wasn't the father?
But the son? Exactly.
And that brought back to me
this myth,
which maybe is not a myth
after all.
That's why I went
to the land registry
this morning before I came here
to look at the records.
And get this -
Erol Karagul's father received
this house by a voluntary transfer
from a man called Pallas in 1942.
Obviously, he needed his friend
to hide his fortune
in those uncertain,
unstable times,
but expected Karagul to give it back
to him after the war.
But now we know Erol's father
never did.
So what if Erol Karagul
knowingly kept his father's secret,
but it took an unimaginable
grief and illness
for him to face up to it?
His wife says he has become...
..very confused since he collapsed.
Even so, why is a disturbed
Muslim man...
..quoting from the Bible?
MESSAGE ALERT
Kemal?
Hey, put the gun down.
I said, put the gun down.
Are you going to shoot me,
Detective Suleyman?
This ends now, yes?
OK. Turn over. OK. Face down.
I was hoping to be able to do
this for at least one more week,
but the police are not going away.
OK.
It's done.
One million euros.
BEEPS HORN
Come on. Easy.
Here you go.
I'll call you a cab back to mine.
I'm fine.
MESSAGE ALERT
You knew what you were.
You knew exactly
where your wealth came from.
You know, if you hadn't made him
complicit in your crimes,
you could have lived.
But now Demir is dead.
And soon you will be too.
No.
Sh. No, no.
It's OK.
QUIET: Help.
What are you doing?!
Erol, wake up.
Please, baby, wake up. Come on.
Cem Bey.
Mrs Karagul, please, allow me.
Erol Bey. What's happening?
Erol Bey.
Erol Bey. Has he got a pulse?
Yes.
How long has she been
giving him the drugs?
I don't know.
She's worked here for three months.
Where the hell have you been?
I lost Cem at a junction, got caught
in traffic trying to find him.
Yeah, right. What are we doing?
Lina's been poisoning Erol.
Did you pass her on the way in? No.
You check the garage. She hasn't
left the perimeter. Keep in contact.
DOG BARKS
We need to try
and keep him conscious.
Erol Bey.
Come on, baby.
You've got to fight.
Oh, God.
Fight for your baby.
Fight for me. Fight for us.
"Do not go gentle
into that good night,
"Old age should burn
and rave at close of day;
"Rage, rage against
the dying of the light.
"Though wise men at their end
know dark is right,
"Because their words
had forked no lightning
"They do not go gentle
into that good night.
"Good men, the last wave by,
crying how bright.
"Their frail deeds might have
danced in a green bay,
"Rage, rage against
the dying of the light."
I've got you, baby. I promise.
"Wild men who caught
and sang the sun in flight
"And learn, too late,
they grieved on its way,
"Do not go gentle
into that good night.
"Grave men, near death,
who see with blinding sight
"Blind eyes could blaze
like meteors and be gay,
"Rage, rage against
the dying of the light."
Lina!
GUNSHOT
"And you, my father,
there on the sad height,
"Curse, bless, me now
with your fierce tears, I pray.
"Do not go gentle
into that good night.
"Rage...
.."rage against
the dying of the light."
Are you OK?
HE SPEAKS IN TURKISH
Eleni Pallas.
Nice to meet you.
So...
..Erol Karagul's father stole
your grandfather's house...
..took advantage of his best friend
in his hour of need.
They stole our house. The artwork.
My grandfather lost everything.
And you came for revenge.
No, I came for justice.
I grew up in poverty.
Meanwhile, they were living
the life that they stole from us.
Eleni, you murdered Demir,
an innocent man.
No-one named Karagul is innocent.
How long were you planning this for?
I mean,
it must have taken some time.
Time away from him.
He will suffer.
He will suffer just like you did.
MESSAGE ALERT
Boss?
Oh... Boss?
Hey, thanks for...
No, you... You'd have done the same.
Maybe.
Hey, where were you?
When you let Cem go?
I told you. Stuck in traffic.
Ayse, I had your back.
Yeah, but you're lying
to me, Mehmet.
You are lying to me.
And until you tell me the truth,
I can't trust you.
And neither can Ikmen.
Serpil.
Shall I order us some food?
This is...
It's over, right?
She loves you anyway.
Chasing this won't change anything.
Just put you both in danger.
All right.
So let me give you this.
I thought... I switched it.
And I cracked the password
before they came.
She loves you, man.
Thank you.
# Olum gelir ani
# Olum gelir ani, olum gelir ani
# Dunya fani
# Dunya fani, dunya fani
# Sonsuz tatil
# Sonsuz tatil, sonsuz tatil
# After party
# After party, after party
# Olum gelir ani
# Olum gelir ani, olum gelir ani
# Dunya fani
# Dunya fani, dunya fani
# Sonsuz tatil
# Sonsuz tatil, sonsuz tatil
# After party
# After party, after party
# Bizim icin zor olan paralar degil
# Gerekirse onlara yaralar
verip hatalara gir
# Bahamalar Gunes
# Birak bahaneleri,
agir agir dus hep
# Bilir dusmanlar, biz dise dise
# Ogrendim bunlara duse duse
# Gerekirse takilir canimiz dise
# Acitamaz canimizi bugun hicbi' sey
# Ama kalkmayi bil
# Sen gorkemli
# Sen erdemli
# Sen sehvetli
# Olum gelir ani
# Olum gelir ani, olum gelir ani
# Dunya fani
# Dunya fani, dunya fani
# Sonsuz tatil
# Sonsuz tatil, sonsuz tatil... #